What is going on everybody?
We have been getting a ton of questions on, uhm,
what company people should be using to get their LLC started,
how they should be setting up their LLC, all kinds of things like that.
And, I had Blake,
I tasked Blake and I was like, hey, can you look around and figure
out a company that will go ahead and build,
you know, LLCs for our students, they'll give them a great deal,
take care of them. And he looked around at a bunch of other places
and he was like, dude, honestly, these places all look like they suck.
So instead, we reached out to the people who actually built our LLCs and
built our corporate, you know, did our entire corporate strategy,
our tax strategy, everything like that,
and reached out to them. And we said, Hey, look, guys, here's what we're
doing over here. We got a community of new entrepreneurs,
people who are looking to, you know, really dig their feet into,
you know, into the business world and we're looking for somebody who can help
them get started the right way. Would you guys be able to be a
solution for that? And they said, look, they're part of your community.
Let's do it. So we've got a special deal for everybody.
Basically, uh, by the way,
the name of it is Prime. I'm corporate services. Um,
there are, no, there's many great things about it, but number one thing you
need to understand is they understand wholesalers,
right? They understand how the income works, everything like that.
And they have a ton of great, uh, tax strategies and just,
uh, corporate strategy of, Hey,
do we set up an LLC or an S corp or a C corp,
which is best, right? They can answer all these questions.
So everybody, just for being a part of my community gets a free 45
minute consultation call with them, where even if you don't set up an LLC
with them, you're going to want to do this because they're going to tell
you about You tons of different things that you can do,
um, write-offs you can secure.
So all that money you're making wholesaling doesn't go to the IRS.
Like for instance, did you know that for joining this program,
that's a write-off, right? They're going to be able to help you out with
things like that. So as I said,
these are the people who set up our business. This is our LLCs,
our corporate structure. Um,
they're really good. They're really trusted in the industry.
Um, so I recommend everybody to jump on it,
schedule a call with them. Even if you already have an LLC,
I'm telling you, these guys are smart.
Okay. Here's something you need to realize.
Every 10% you can save on your taxes is 10% you just added into
your bank account, right? That's like increasing the amount of money you made by
10%. And if you can do that real quick in 45 minutes,
it's the most worth it phone call you might have all year.
All right. So everybody, the link is down below when you use that link,
you get a free consultation call. They're going to take care of you.
Um, and they're doing it all at a great price.
If you do need to set up an LLC or your corporate structure.
All right. So go ahead, check it out with them.
Let me know how it goes. Send me a message. If you have any
questions.